<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Exclusive support for you and your body]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Exclusive support for you and your body]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/collagen-boutique/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 00:52:31 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/collagen-boutique/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/cc692286-a906-42aa-9ac7-0cc1bcea9fed.png">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/collagen-boutique/here-i-amm-with-the-new-webpage-dedicated-to-brilliant-produ/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e7bd75db-1978-49a6-859e-27fc1d8df66c</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 00:46:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Collagen Native GOLD]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Collagen Native GOLD</h1><p>Gold Native Collagen is a pure collagen formula enriched with substances that have antibacterial, anti-inflammatory, anti-microbial, antifungal and general regenerative properties. It also demonstrates powerful anti-aging properties. Designed for people with problematic and hypersensitive skin, prone to discolourations, lichens and eczemas. Synergy of colloidal gold with collagen peptides acts according to the ionic pump principle: it speeds up the migration of active substances and exchange of microelements as well as stimulates the transdermal cleansing process. It prevents discolourations and has soothing, antibacterial and biostimulating properties. Lactoferrin, responsible for collagen gel’s its light pink tint, is a bioactive protein with anti-inflammatory and anti-acne properties.Always cleanse the skin with water prior to collagen application. Biologically active collagen peptides are better absorbed if the gel is delicately patted on moist skin, not rubbed in. The best and even most spectacular effects of na¬tive collagen are seen when applied immediately after peeling. It is strongly recommended that the collagen be applied to the face, neck and cleavage twice daily, in the morning and in the evening. Irritated or burned skin requires the application of as much collagen as can be absorbed. The first effects of the product are clearly felt as soon as several minutes after the application of the gel.</p><img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/vahj1ThiexotieMo/fcd4633a029b022e59d32c4f5d2928d1/noop.png?input=https%3A%2F%2Fcolwayinternational.com%2Fshop%2Fitem%2F9861%2Fb66e206bacb15dde84b0e412274d2c451d36991a-img.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://graf.colwayinternational.com/shop/products/7/21,collagen-native-gold.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f34a65de-dfee-4946-af6d-26ea05b7ccaa</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 00:52:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Collagen Native DNA - keep your DNA safe!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Collagen Native DNA - keep your DNA safe!</h1><p>The depreciation of the skin begins due to two reasons: </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/51cb2c7b62538e178ebd38a2d12b196b38102b49.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/collagen-boutique/collagen-native-dna-keep-your-dna-safe/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7487681d-3b79-46e4-856c-5e26f71f2a96</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 00:47:31 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>